Hello, I'm Ten-ten.
Hello, I'm Chigasaki.
I'm Jigen.
Oh, the one who was just in the water
tank.
Oharu-san.
I should change my clothes.
No, you shouldn't.
Pink doesn't suit you.
It suits me!
No, it's a throbbing pink.
I like pink, but this pink doesn't suit
me.
I'm usually not like this.
No, I thought you were amazing.
It suits you. It suits you so well.
It's already perfect.
I've been wearing it for 6 years, but
it doesn't suit me.
I agree.
It's amazing.
Which one do you like?
Mine?
I had two sandwiches for lunch, but I
had one more with my manager.
I had half of it.
I was full.
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to our channel!
I'm not sure if I can watch it again.
Change the frame.
I'll insert the Jiria.
I can't use it.
It's like a re-use.
Ice cake.
I'm excited even though I'm not the
main character.
I think I ate it.
I think so too.
I was wondering if you ate it.
I don't know.
We don't eat it.
I think I ate it.
I think so too.
I don't know.
I want to take it home.
I want to put it in the train.
I want to put it in my head.
I want to take it home.
It's cute.
I have never put it in my head.
Buzz?
I also have Disney.
I want to buy it.
Disney is cute.
I want to hold that and make it look
like I'm holding it.
The one that you hold a lot?
It's pretty popular.
I want to hold a lot of balloons and
make it look like I'm holding it.
If you're a staff, you can put it here
and let it go.
That's how you do it.
It's like I'm holding it.
That was the knowledge of the slug.
It's been a while since I've heard
this.
Oh, from now on, Tokiboro...
I'm sorry.
Why?
So...
I'll do my best in part 2.
Bye-bye.
What are we talking about?
It's just a chat.
It's cute.
I'm scared.
This program is a program where six
people who are active to promote
Tokimeki Monito challenge various things
and raise the barometer of Tokimeki in
the world.
I will prove it to you.
How about this?
I like it.
How about pink?
I'm TAKIMUKI Pink.
This pink color looks good on me.
I'm getting rid of my eyebrows.
I want to make it look like a twin.
How do you like it?
I've only done one hair style today.
I'm not sure if I can eat it.
I think the bento looks delicious.
The bento looks delicious.
I've never had it before.
I'll eat it tomorrow.
I feel like I'm going to get a pimple.
I don't know.
See you next week!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Here comes the healthy mom!
Why did you get a eye injection?
I'm not wearing sunglasses, so I can't
go out.
Oh, you're not wearing sunglasses, so
you can't go out.
I'll do my best at the Tsuriyama Seikan
Festival!
Bye bye!
Subscribe to my channel!
I was singing.
Hello.
The next world tour will start in less
than an hour.
I'm Julia Imai, 21 years old.
Thank you to subscribe the channel and
share on social networks.
See you!
I drank the cider of July
I can't forget that night
It hurts, it hurts, I can't help but
feel lonely
The streetlights are a little dim
I'm waiting for you, my heart is
pounding
Your voice is...
January.
I said it clearly.
It's January.
I thought I said it wrong.
The first day of the concert was a
success!
It was amazing.
It was great.
The 2021 JuriJuri Arena will start
soon!
I was on stage alone at the solo
concert last year.
This is the second time.
The point of the costume is...
It's not something you can see all the
time, but it's a big ribbon that you can
see from behind.
When I sing solo, there is a song that
starts with a back view.
I'm sure everyone will think it's cute
when they see it.
It's my favorite point.
It's on the other side of the screen,
but...
I hope I can show you a powerful
performance to the point where I can
deliver a lot of excitement to the other
side of the screen.
Please look forward to it! I'll do my
best!
I've been cutting for 30 minutes.
I'll do my best.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Julia Lee's Birthday Party!
If you think I look good in this
costume,
and if you like Julia Lee because she
is cute,
please subscribe to my channel and
click the good button.
Bye bye!
See you next week!
What's that?
What?
I don't know.
It's not a person.
Kanami, Chubiya, Hitoka, Naruka, Haki,
Riori, Super Tekimeki Tenden, Rock'n!
I'm going to sing a singing song of
love and
Bye bye!
Oh, hold on, you'll do me okay
Don't cry, it's here
Don't cry, it's a thread
Don't cry, it's a kiss
Once you bite it, you can't let go
You can't let go
The lion is shaking from the wind
The lion is running today
The days I spent with you
I'm sure it's not in vain
Even if it hurts, even if it hurts
I'm going to overcome the pain
But I'm glad I didn't cry
I found the end of the road I kept
running
I want to deliver the best melody of my
life
I want to sing with all my might
I won't lose, I'll shout again and
again
I heard the best melody of my life
I'm glad I didn't cry
I'm glad I didn't cry.
The lyrics tell the story of Julia.
I'm the father.
Who is it?
I'm Julia's father.
I'll read it.
To the publicity staff who always
support me.
I turned 17 on the 15th of this month.
This is the third time I've been
invited to the Toki Festival.
I've never had so many people celebrate
my birthday.
I'm so happy to receive a birthday
message.
Thank you for your support.
At the birthday party, I was alone at
the stage for the first time last year.
I was nervous at the time, but I
thought it was a lot of fun.
I was very happy to be able to do it
again this year.
In 2020, I think there were times when
you felt dark and lost confidence.
But at that time, I was supported by
the message from the publicity staff.
I'm not used to being praised.
I'm happy to hear that I'm a good
dancer.
I'll do my best to overcome it.
I was like that a year ago.
I couldn't express myself at that time.
But now, the Toki Festival is a very
strong bond.
It's warm and comfortable.
I can relax and enjoy Toki Festival
activities from the bottom of my heart.
I'm grateful to the publicity staff who
made such a place.
I want to make more memories with
everyone in 2021.
I want to make everyone smile.
I want to do my best at the age of 17.
Please continue to support me.
I'm going to do my best.
Happy birthday to you! Happy birthday
to you! Happy birthday dear Jiyu!
Oh, I was surprised.
Happy birthday to you!
Thank you!
Cute!
It's a straw.
It smells good.
Cute!
How is it?
It smells like fruity.
Does it smell like fruity?
Yes, it does.
It smells different.
Try again.
It's sweet!
I see.
You guys are the ones who want to make
me say it.
It was fruity.
It's sweet!
It feels good.
It matches the costume.
It's so cute.
I got a cake.
It's heavy.
Thank you.
It was cute.
I was nervous.
I'm sorry.
What was that?
When you were practicing self-
introduction?
When Julia first came on stage,
we practiced self-introduction.
We practiced shaking hands.
Julia and I shook hands once.
We did a lot of things.
Julia was so proud.
She was full of confidence on stage.
She was so confident.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
I'm going to bend the spoon.
It's bent.
It's bent a lot.
It's bent a little.
I'm going to start from here.
I can't do it.
You're going to fall.
I'm going to fall.
I think you can do it.
I can't do it.
You're amazing.
It's MAJI.
Cool.
I'm done.
I remember the time when we met
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a sunny pattern
I play the sound of a rainbow
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a sunny pattern
I cry my tears out
I wear a rainbow dress